Dear Christmas is a tv movie, romance film directed by Emily Moss Wilson.
Natalie Morgan is an author and host of a popular podcast, Holiday Love,
which shares true stories of holiday romance with its listeners.
While to the outside world and her listeners everywhere see Natalie is an expert
on romance, she's never truly experienced a romance of her own.
As Natalie prepares to embark on a promotional tour for her new book, she stops back home to spend Christmas with her family and to celebrate her
parent's 50th anniversary where she unexpectedly begins to experience her own holiday romance as sparks ignite with local firefighter, Jack.
Natalie Morgan, played by Melissa Joan Hart.
Chris Massey, played by Jason Priestley.
Jenny Morgan, played by Faith Prince.
Randy Morgan, played by Ed Begley Jr..
Penny, played by Robin Givens.
Emma, played by Nicky Whelan.
Dear God is a 1996 American comedy film directed by Garry
Marshall and starring Greg Kinnear and Laurie Metcalf.
Kinnear stars as Tom Turner, a con artist who gets a job at the dead letter office of a
post office, and finds his life changing after reading letters sent to God.
The song of the same title by Midge Ure was used in the
film's theatrical trailer and in the film itself.
Dear God was released by Paramount Pictures on November 1,
1996 to mostly negative reviews from critics.
The film was a box office bomb, grossing
$7,138,523 against a $22 million budget.
The tone is emotional.